William Edgar Borah Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Office File, 1907-1940 (Box 1-528)
  - 1922-1923 (Box 127)
    - Farm legislation
    - Feaster, Dick
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal farm loans, (3 folders)
    - Federal land bank legislation (Box 132)
    - Federal Reserve, (2 folders)
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
      - Clemenceau
      - Europe, (3 folders)
      - Occupation of Ruhr Valley, Germany, (2 folders)
      - Reparations
      - Miscellaneous
    - Foreign trade (Box 133)
    - Freight rates
    - Funding foreign debt
    - Garvey, Marcus
    - General information, (2 folders)
    - Gold and silver
    - Gooding Bill
    - Gwinn, Monte
    - Haiti
    - Hart, John W.
    - Hileman, G. J.
    - Immigration
      - General
      - Legislation
    - Increase in salary
    - Indian
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Internal Revenue, (1 folder) (Box 134)
    - International Conference, (3 folders)
    - International Court proposal, (2 folders)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Intolerance
    - Invitations
      - Visit to Europe
      - Arizona-Arkansas, (2 folders)
      - California-Maine, (15 folders) (Box 135)
      - Maryland-New York, (13 folders) (Box 136)
      - New York City-Wisconsin, (18 folders) (Box 137)
    - Irish Republic
    - Justice Department
    - Ku Klux Klan
    - Labor Department
    - Lasley, Sue
    - League of Nations (Box 138)
    - Legislation, miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Legislative record
    - Le Moyne residence, Boise, Idaho
    - Letters
      - Introduction
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - Livestock
    - Long and short haul legislation (Box 139)
    - Mayfield, Earle B.
    - McConnell, W. J.
    - Miscellaneous, (6 folders)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National banks
    - Naturalization (Box 140)
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Navy
    - Newspapers, (3 folders)
    - Nicaragua
    - Outlawing of war, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 141)
    - Panama Canal
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Patronage
      - Appointments closed
      - Appointments, Alfred Budge
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal
      - Public record
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, (2 folders)
    - Petroleum (Box 142)
    - Photographs, requests for
    - Political
      - Idaho, (2 folders)
      - Third party movement
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, (2 folders)
    - Post Office Department, (2 folders)
    - Presidential nomination (Box 143)
    - Price fixing
    - Primary, national
    - Primary law, Idaho
    - Prohibition
    - Puerto Rico
    - Railroads
    - Reese, Jefferson
    - Requests for speeches
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia, (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - Seeds
    - Ship subsidy
    - Shipping board
    - Soldiers
      - Compensation
      - Legislation
    - Statements, correspondence relating to
    - Sterling-Lehlbach
    - Sterling-Towner Bill
    - Sugar
    - Supreme Court
    - Sweet, Willis
    - Tariff
    - Taxation
    - Transfers (Box 145)
    - Treasury Department
    - U.S. Employees' Compensation Act
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Vocational training, (3 folders)
    - Watson, James E.
    - West Point, N. Y., United States Military Academy
    - White Radio bill
    - Wyman, Frank T.
  - 1923-1924 (Box 146)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Agriculture legislation, (2 folders)
    - Alien property custodian
    - Amnesty
    - Applications
      - Pardons, (1 folder) (Box 147)
      - Positions
        - A-R, (4 folder)
        - S-R (Box 148)
    - Appointments
    - Appropriations
    - Army
    - Articles
      - "Outlaw War"
      - Requests for
    - Banking legislation
    - Bergdoll, Grover Cleveland
    - Birth control
    - Bok, Edward S., (2 folders) (Box 149)
    - Bonus
    - Bursum Bill (Indian legislation)
    - Business
      - Baird house
      - Income tax
      - Personal
      - Miscellaneous
    - Campaign expenditures
      - Evidence
      - Witness (Box 150)
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Capital News
    - Charity
    - Child labor
    - Citizenship
    - Civil rights bill
    - Civil Service
    - Claims, (2 folders)
    - Coal legislation (Box 151)
    - Committees, (3 folders)
    - Condolence, letters of
    - Congress, "Trading with the Enemy Act"
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Dewey, Edward H.
    - Disarmament
    - Discharge
      - Army
      - Certificates
      - Marine Corps
      - Navy
    - Documents (Box 152)
      - General
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Education Bureau, establishment of
    - Educational rights
    - Equal rights bill
    - Fact Finding Commission
    - Federal farm loan, (3 folders)
    - Federal Reserve, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 153)
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
      - Europe
      - Ruhr Valley, Germany
      - Miscellaneous
    - Free speech
    - Freight rates
    - General, (2 folders)
    - Haiti
    - Hart, John W.
    - Hopkins, J. A. H.
    - Idaho State Penitentiary, Boise, Idaho (Box 154)
    - Immigration, (3 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Increase in salary
    - Indian
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Internal Revenue
    - International Court (Box 155)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations to campaign
      - Idaho
      - National ticket
    - Invitations (by state)
      - California-Idaho, (7 folders)
      - North Carolina-Washington, (11 folders) (Box 156)
    - Justice Department (Box 157)
    - Ku Klux Klan
    - Labor
    - Law enforcement
    - Lesley, Sue
    - Legislation, (6 folders) (Box 158)
    - Letters (Box 159)
      - Introduction
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - Long and short haul bill
    - Mare Island, Calif.
    - McConnell, W. J.
    - McNary-Haugen Bill, (2 folders)
    - Memorial Bridge, Washington, D. C.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 160)
      - Dec. 1923-Sept. 1924, (6 folders)
      - Oct.-Nov. 1924 (Box 161)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National banks
    - National defense test
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Navy, Denby Resolution
    - Navy
      - Legislation
      - Matters
    - Newspapers, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 162)
    - Nicaragua
    - Oil leasing, (2 folders)
    - Outlawing of war
    - Panama Canal
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Patronage
      - Appointments
        - Anderson, Albert B
        - Budge, Alfred (Box 163)
        - Secretary of interior, Nov. 1924
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal
    - Photographs requests
    - Political
      - Appointments and positions
      - Delegates, state and national convention
      - General
        - Dec. 1923-Feb. 1924
        - Mar.-Nov. 1924, (3 folders) (Box 164)
      - Miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - National Committee, appointments with (Box 165)
      - Personal, Sept.-Nov. 1924, (2 folders)
      - Vice president, Apr.-June 1924
    - Puerto Rico
    - Post Office Department
      - General
      - Legislation, (1 folder) (Box 166)
    - Primary
    - Prohibition
    - Public Health Service
    - Quarantine
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation, (2 folders)
    - Reclassification
    - Requests
      - Fact Finding Commission Report
      - Hearings
      - Speeches
    - Rivers and harbors (Box 167)
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia, (2 folders)
    - Seeds
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Soldier legislation
      - Dec. 1923-Feb. 1924, (2 folders)
      - Mar.-June 1924 (Box 168)
    - Spy system, Burton K. Wheeler.
    - Sterling-Towner-Reed Bill, Dec. 1923-Nov. 1924, (2 folders)
    - Supreme Court, five- to- four decisions bill
    - Tariff
    - Taxes
      - Alcohol
      - Exempt securities
      - Income
      - Jewelry
      - Telegraph and telephone
      - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 169)
    - Teapot Dome Scandal
    - Transfers
    - Transportation Act
    - Treaties
    - Treasury Department
    - United States Sugar Equalization Board
    - Veterans Bureau
      - Johnson, Royal C.
      - General
    - Veterans Hospital (Box 170)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Act
    - Vocational training, (2 folders)
    - Votes, record of
    - War Finance Corp.
    - West Point, N. Y., United States Military Academy
    - Wheeler, Burton K.
      - Investigation
      - Senate trial
    - Wyman, Frank T.
  - 1924-1925 (Box 171)
    - Agriculture
    - Agriculture Department
    - Alaska situation
    - Alien property
      - Custodian
      - Legislation, (1 folder) (Box 172)
    - Amnesty
    - Applications for pardons, (2 folders)
    - Applications for positions
      - A-G, (2 folders)
      - H-W, (56 folders) (Box 173)
    - Appointments, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - Appropriations
    - Army matters
    - Articles, (2 folders)
    - Aviation investigation
    - Bank legislation
    - Belgium debt
    - Bonus
    - Business (Box 175)
      - Lodge
      - Taxes, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Campaign expenditures, (2 folders)
    - Charity
    - Child labor amendment
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Citizens' Military Training Camps
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Service
    - Claims, (3 folders) (Box 176)
    - Cloture
    - Coal legislation
    - Committee matters
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Constitution
    - Cooperation marketing
    - Cuba
    - Cummins-Vaile Bill (Box 177)
    - Daylight savings
    - Disarmament, history of
    - Discharge
      - Army
      - Certificates
      - Marine Corps
      - Navy
    - Documents
      - General
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Economic conference
    - Education legislation
    - Federal Farm Loan
    - Federal Reserve banks
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
      - Europe
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 178)
    - Foreign Relations Committee
    - Free speech
    - Freight rates
    - Fuller, Percy J.
    - General, (2 folders)
    - Haiti, French debt, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 179)
    - Hungarian trials
    - Immigration, (2 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Increase in salary
    - Indian (Box 180)
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Internal Revenue
    - International xourts, (4 folders)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations (by state) (Box 181)
      - California-Kansas, (16 folders)
      - Kentucky-New York City, (13 folders) (Box 182)
      - New York City-Virginia, (15 folders) (Box 183)
      - Washington-Wisconsin, (3 folders) (Box 184)
    - Justice Department
    - Kellor, Frances
    - Labor Department
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Law enforcement
    - Legislation
      - Religious
      - Miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Letters (Box 185)
      - Introduction
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - Long and short haul bill
    - Memorial Bridge, Washington, D.C.
    - Mexico
    - Miscellaneous
      - Dec. 1924-Mar. 1925
      - Mar.-Nov. 1925, (5 folders) (Box 186)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala. (Box 187)
    - National banks, (2 folders)
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Naval
      - Legislation
      - Matters
    - Newspapers, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 188)
    - Nicaragua
    - North Dakota senatorial contest
    - Outlawry of war
    - Panama Canal
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Patronage and appointments
      - Agriculture Commission
      - Budge, Alfred
      - Interstate Commerce Commission
      - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 189)
      - Pension Commission
      - Secretary of agriculture
      - Secretary of labor
      - Stone, Harlan Fiske
      - U.S. District Attorney, Idaho
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - Public (Box 190)
    - Philippine Islands
    - Political
      - General
      - Idaho, miscellaneous
      - National Committee, appointment with
      - Miscellaneous
      - Senatorship, Idaho
    - Puerto Rico
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 191)
    - Prohibition
    - Public Health Service
    - Reclassification
    - Rent bill
    - Requests for
      - Hearing
      - Photographs
      - Speeches, (2 folders)
      - Treaties
    - Rinard, Mattie
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia (Box 192)
    - Saklatvala, Shapurji
    - Salary increase
    - Samoa
    - Seeds
    - Soldier legislation
    - Tariff legislation
    - Taxation
    - Transfers (Box 193)
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans hospitals
    - Vocational training, (2 folders)
    - Warren confirmation
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - Wheeler, Burton K.
    - World Court
  - 1925-1926 (Box 194)
    - Agriculture Department, (2 folders)
    - Agriculture legislation, (2 folders)
    - Alaska
    - Alien property
      - Custodian
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Investigation, (2 folders) (Box 195)
      - Newton Bill
    - Amnesty
    - Antilynching law
    - Applications
      - Pardons
      - Positions
        - A-D, (2 folders)
        - E-W, (6 folders) (Box 196)
    - Appointments, (2 folders) (Box 197)
    - Appropriations
    - Army
    - Army-Navy football tickets
    - Articles, (2 folders)
    - Bank legislation (Box 198)
    - Boise barracks, Boise, Idaho
    - Bonus
    - Business
      - Income tax
      - Lodge dues
      - Miscellaneous
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charity
    - China
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Service
    - Claims (Box 199)
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Kelly, Mary, (3 folders)
    - Cloture
    - Coal
    - Coconut oil
    - Colored question
    - Committee matters (Box 200)
    - Condolence letters
    - Congratulation
    - Congressional Library lists
    - Congressional Record
    - Constitution
    - Cooperative marketing
    - Cuban investigation
    - Discharge
      - Army
      - Navy
    - Documents
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Disarmament, (2 folders)
    - Education, legislation (Box 201)
    - Embassy courier letter
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal farm loan
    - Federal Loan Act
    - Federal Reserve banks
    - Federal tort claims bill
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
    - Foreign debt
    - Freight rates
    - French debt (Box 202)
    - Fuller, Percy J.
    - General, (3 folders)
    - German bonds
    - Haiti
    - Hoover, Herbert
    - House bills, status of
    - Immigration, (3 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Increase in salary
    - Indian (Box 203)
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Internal Revenue
    - Invitations (by state)
      - Alabama-Delaware, (9 folders)
      - District of Columbia-Indiana, (7 folders) (Box 204)
      - Iowa-New Hampshire, (13 folders) (Box 205)
      - New Jersey-Oklahoma, (8 folders) (Box 206)
      - Oregon-Wyoming, (14 folders) (Box 207)
    - Japanese acquiring land in lower California (Box 208)
    - Justice Department
    - Kellor, Frances
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Legislation, (5 folders)
    - Letters (Box 209)
      - Introduction, (2 folders)
      - Recommendation
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - Long and short haul, Gooding Bill
    - Longshoreman's compensation bill
    - McCormick, Mrs. Medill
    - Mail contracts
    - Mexico
    - Military training (Box 210)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Dec. 1925-Aug. 1926, (6 folders)
      - Sept.-Nov. 1926, (2 folders) (Box 211)
    - Movie legislation
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National banks
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Navy matters
    - Newspapers, (3 folders) (Box 212)
    - Nicaragua
    - Outlawry of war
    - Panama (Box 213)
    - Passaic strike, (3 folders)
    - Passport control (S. 1091)
    - Passports
    - Patents, (2 folders)
    - Patronage (Box 214)
      - Alaska appointments
      - Budge, Alfred
      - Closed
      - Slattery
      - Miscellaneous
    - Pension legislation, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 215)
    - Personal
      - Biography
      - Miscellaneous
    - Philippine
      - Independence
      - Legislation
    - Political
      - Government ship, Idaho
      - Idaho, miscellaneous
      - Personal
      - Special, Borah
      - Stephenson, D.C., matter in Indiana
      - United States Senatorship, Idaho (Box 216)
      - Vare-Smith investigation
      - Miscellaneous
      - Puerto Rico
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation
    - Primary elections
    - Prohibition, (2 folders)
    - Public Health Service (Box 217)
    - Radio legislation
    - Railroad legislation
    - Requests for
      - Bills
      - Hearings and reports
      - Photographs
      - Speeches
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Robins, Raymond
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Rubber
    - Russia (Box 218)
    - Saklatvala, Shapurji
    - Salaries, increase of
    - Schreiner, George A.
    - Seeds
    - Sheppard-Towner Maternity Bill
    - Tariff
    - Taxes
      - Inheritance
      - Capital stock
    - Taxation
    - Taxation, community property matters (Box 219)
    - Transfers
    - Transportation
    - United States Coast Guard
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Hospital
    - Vocational education
    - Vocational training
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - Wheeler, Burton K.
    - Wheeler Resolution No. 88
    - World Court
      - Dec. 1925-Jan. 1926, (6 folders)
      - Jan.-May 1926, (11 folders) (Box 220)
    - World Court expenses
    - Wyman, Frank T.
  - 1926-1927 (Box 221)
    - Agricultural legislation, (2 folders)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Alien property custodian
    - Alien property legislation, (3 folders)
    - Applications for pardons (Box 222)
    - Applications for positions
      - A-S, (5 folders)
      - T-W (Box 223)
      - Chaplain of the Senate
      - Washington, D.C., boys who wish to attend school
    - Appointments, (2 folders)
    - Appropriations
    - Army matters
    - Army-Navy football game
    - Articles, granted
    - Bank legislation (Box 224)
    - Bonus
    - Borah for President, (2 folders)
    - Bread trust investigation
    - Business
      - Income
      - Lodge dues
      - Miscellaneous
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charity
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Service exam, United States Military Academy West Point, N.Y. (Box 225)
    - Claims, (3 folders)
    - Coal
    - Committee matters
    - Condolence letters
    - Congratulation
    - Congressional Library list
    - Congressional Record
    - Constitution
    - Costa Rica
    - Customs
    - Disarmament, history of (Box 226)
    - Discharges
      - Army
      - Navy
    - Documents
    - Educational matters
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal farm loan
    - Federal Reserve banks
    - Federal Reserve System
    - Fish
    - Foreign
      - Affairs
      - Letters
    - French debt
    - General, (2 folders)
    - Haiti (Box 227)
    - Immigration, (3 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Indian
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations
      - Alabama-foreign countries, (9 folders)
      - Georgia-Massachusetts, (13 folders) (Box 228)
      - Massachusetts-New York City, (13 folders) (Box 229)
      - New York City-Vermont, (14 folders) (Box 230)
      - Virginia-Wyoming, (5 folders) (Box 231)
    - Judge Ferrington's delayed decision
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Legislation, miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Letters
      - Introduction
      - Recommendation (Box 232)
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Lists
    - Long and short haul, Gooding Bill
    - Mail contract
    - Mexico, (5 folders)
    - Mexico and the Catholic Church
    - Miscellaneous, (6 folders) (Box 233)
    - Mississippi River flood disaster
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.. (Box 234)
    - National banks
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Navy matters
    - Newspapers, (4 folders)
    - Nicaragua, (2 folders)
    - Oil
    - Outlawry of war (Box 235)
    - Panama
    - Passports
    - Patents and inventions
    - Patronage and appointments
      - Alaska
      - Budge, Alfred
      - Dietrich, Judge, (3 folders)
      - Federal Board of Vocational Education
      - Interstate Commerce Commission
      - Langley, C. L.
      - Morrow, Dwight
      - Prohibition commissioner
      - Prohibition director, Idaho (Box 236)
      - Tilson, William J.
      - Miscellaneous
    - Pension
    - Personal, (2 folders)
    - Philippine legislation
    - Political
      - Idaho, miscellaneous
      - Personal
      - Smith-Vare
      - Third term
      - Miscellaneous
    - Puerto Rico
    - Post Office Department
    - Post Office legislation (Box 237)
    - Prohibition, (3 folders)
    - Prohibition Fifteenth Amendment
    - Public Health Service
    - Radio
    - Radio legislation, (2 folders)
    - Railroad legislation
    - Requests for
      - Articles, (2 folders)
      - Bills (Box 238)
      - Hearings, general reports, treaties
      - Photographs
      - Speeches
    - Rinard, Mattie
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Rockwell, Irwin E.
    - Russia
    - Sacco-Vanzetti case
    - Salaries, increase of
    - Schreiner, George A.
    - Seeds
    - Sheppard-Towner Act
    - Soldier's Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Swing-Johnson Bill
    - Taxation (Box 239)
    - Transfers
    - Treasury Department
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans Hospital, (2 folders)
    - Washburn, R. M.
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - World Court
  - 1927-1928 (Box 240)
    - Admiralty treaties
    - Agricultural legislation, (4 folders)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Alien property
      - Custodian
      - Investigation
    - Amnesty (Box 241)
    - Applications
      - Pardons
      - Positions
        - A-H, (3 folders)
        - I-W, (3 folders) (Box 242)
    - Appointments with Borah
    - Appropriations
    - Army
      - Legislation
      - Matters
    - Articles, granted
    - Bank legislation (Box 243)
    - Bonds
    - Bonus
    - Borah for President
    - Boulder Dam
    - Business
      - Lodge dues
      - Taxes
      - Miscellaneous
      - Yeamans, E. Wignote
    - Business income tax
    - Cavanah, Charles C. (Box 244)
    - Charity
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Citizenship
    - Claims, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 245)
    - Coal
    - Coast Guard
    - Committee matters
    - Committee Treaty of Trianon
    - Congressional Record
    - Constitution
    - Cuban investigation
    - Customs
    - Disarmament, history of
    - Discharges
      - Army
      - Marine Corps
      - Navy
    - Documents (Box 246)
      - General
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Educational matters
    - Eighteenth Amendment
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal farm loan
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
      - Miscellaneous
      - Letters
    - Foreign Service Building Commission
    - Frazier Resolution, (2 folders) (Box 247)
    - Freight rates
    - French debt
    - General, (2 folders)
    - Haiti
    - Hart, John W.
    - Hay, Elliot, Fur Seal Treaty
    - Imbrie, Robert Whitney, (2 folders)
    - Immigration, (3 folders) (Box 248)
    - Increase in salaries
    - Indian affairs
    - International Trade Exposition, New Orleans, La.
    - Investigation under La Follette Resolution
    - Invitations (Box 249)
      - Alabama-Maryland, (17 folders)
      - Massachusetts-New York City, (12 folders) (Box 250)
      - North Carolina-Wyoming, (18 folders) (Box 251)
      - Isle of Pines, (2 folders) (Box 252)
    - Karolyi, Count
    - Lasley, Sue
    - Lausanne Treaty, (4 folders)
    - Legislation, miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 253)
    - Letters